tylerperry.com 2014-12-13

# Privacy Policy — TylerPerry.com

## Tyler Perry Studios Online Privacy Policy

Tyler Perry Studios respects the privacy concerns of the users of its Internet Sites (“Sites”), and has created this privacy statement to explain what information we gather from your visit to our Sites, and how such information may be used.

**Use of Information:**

As a general policy no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or e-mail address, is automatically collected from your visit to Tyler Perry Studios Sites. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of Tyler Perry Studios’s Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your IP address is gathered in order to enhance your online experience.

Our Sites’ various registration forms and surveys may request that you give us contact information (such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address) demographic information (such as your age and gender) and profile data (such as your preferences in entertainment). Information submitted at the time of registration or submission may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Tyler Perry Studios and its subsidiaries, and may be shared with our promotional partners. Personally identifiable information is never sold or leased to any third parties. With your permission, we may use your contact information to send you information about our companies and what we’re doing. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Choice/Opt-out section below.

Our Sites use various order forms for you to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address), and when appropriate, financial information (your credit card number) to process your request or purchase. Contact information from an order form is used to fulfill orders, and to provide information about our company to you if requested. The contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary regarding your order. Financial information that is collected is used to process your request for products and services, and will not be shared with third parties who are not involved with the transaction. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. 

Tyler Perry Studios may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with Tyler Perry Studios’s rights or property, other Tyler Perry Studios web site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

To the extent that any of our Sites accessible through the URL www.TylerPerry.com have additional or different practices or policies, these practices will be explained at that Site.

**Security:**

Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Tyler Perry Studios cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

**Use of Cookies:**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using our Sites easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. As an example, we use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart when you visit our online store, and help identify you when you return to the Store. These cookies are restricted for use only on our Sites, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. (Note: you will need to consult the help area of your browser application for instructions.) If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of Tyler Perry Studios’s web sites will not function properly or may be considerably slower. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set personalized preferences or you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, entering contests, or playing games.

**Use of IP Addresses:**

An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet provider whenever you’re surfing the Web. When you requests pages from Tyler Perry Studios Sites, our servers log your IP address. Tyler Perry Studios collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our Site. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you anonymous to us. We may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Sites, customers, or others.

**Links to Other Sites:**

Tyler Perry Studios is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to our Sites. Our Sites may also be linked to websites operated by other companies. Visitors to these web sites should refer to each web site’s respective privacy policies and practices.

**Message Boards and Chat Areas:**

Guests of Tyler Perry Studios Sites are solely responsible for the content of messages they post on public forums, such as chat rooms and message boards. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., user name, e-mail address, phone number) on the public section of the message boards or in the chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people.

**Choice/Opt-Out:**

Our Sites may provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us at the point where we request information about you. You always have the option of removing your name from any e-mail list to not receive future communications. In order to ensure immediate removal from any list, it is best to follow the specific instructions outlined within the communications you receive from us since Tyler Perry Studios operates numerous sites tailored to specific interests. However, if you are unable to complete the process indicated in the communications, [contact the site administrator](mailto:siteadmin@tylerperry.net) with a copy of the undesired email attached to the request and state you wish to be removed from the mailing list. 

**Contact Us:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our Sites, or your dealings with our Sites, you can [contact the site administrator](mailto:siteadmin@tylerperry.net) . 

Information provided by you via general e-mail inquiries to Tyler Perry Studios such as your e-mail address is used only to respond to your inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never shared with third parties.

To view educational material on consumer privacy, please see [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

**Your Acceptance of These Terms:**

By using Tyler Perry Studios’s Sites, you signify your acceptance of the Tyler Perry Studios Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Sites. Tyler Perry Studios reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time. Should Tyler Perry Studios modify, alter or otherwise update this policy, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail at the last e-mail address that you provided us, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Websites covered by this Privacy Policy. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or our posting of the notice of the changes on the Websites covered by this Privacy Policy. Please note: you are responsible, at all times, for updating your personal information within your profile maintained by us and providing us with your current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address provided by you to us is invalid, or for any other reason is not capable of delivering the notification to you, then the notification sent by us to you will constitute effective notice of the changes to this Privacy Policy.

Last updated April 14, 2007

© 2011 My.Ty.Pe. Productions for Tyler Perry Studios  
All rights reserved. Do not duplicate or redistribute in any form.
